sweetsharing.com 2019-10-31

# PRIVACY POLICY - Sweet Sharing

**Sweet Sharing.com** Privacy Policy purpose is to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making accurate decisions when using our site, products and services.

## 1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE

 ** _Contact  Information_**  
You will provide us information about yourself and your firm or company when you try to contact us using our contact form on our **[contact page](https://www.sweetsharing.com/contact/ "https://www.sweetsharing.com/contact/").**

 ** _Email Information  
_**If you choose to reach us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

 ** _Comment  Information_**  
Sweetsharing.com encourages users active participation through comments on our blog posts. However we have no control on the information you disclose publicly  on our website. This information can be viewed or collected by other websites, third parties and users who access our website.

### 2\. WEBSITE USE INFORMATION

Like other  websites, this site uses a standard technology called **cookies** and Web server logs to collect information about how this site is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits,  time spent at this site, the pages viewed and the websites visited just before and just after our site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them. This is a general practice when you visit any website.

## What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as how you browse the site.

### What Are Cookies?

 **A cookie** is a small text document sent by the website which stores in user’s browser. It contains user information like how user interacted with particular website, what type of information he/she has gone through. This type of information helps websites to serve you better. For example advertising companies like Google AdSense use cookies to show relevant ads based on your previous browsing history. For each user an unique cookie will gets created.

Cookies help us understand what is the information you browsed on our site, what is the device, operating system you used to browse our website, your demographics information like region, country, city and language. This information is used by third parties like Google Analytics for generating reports. You can control your cookies in your browser settings to block websites from setting cookies in your browser.

## How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?

Frankly speaking, we use personal information for different purposes like administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and likely customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking the unsubscribe link contained in each such email.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

The information we collect is used to improve the content of this site and the quality of our service, and is not shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes. That being said, your information could be shared under the following circumstances:

  * We use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, these third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with those business activities.
  * As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions.
  * We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.
  * If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected fraud, illegal activities, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

## How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?

We don’t recommend users to send their personal information via email. Although most of the email websites use HTTPS encryption still we hear in news hackers disclosing users secure information online. Information you send using our website forms is secured by SSL (secured sockets layer) encryption.

## Notice of New Services and Changes

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to this website, special offers and new services. If you are not willing to receive our email updates you can unsubscribe to our newsletters by simply clicking on unsubscribe link which we place in every email.

##  Disclosures

We may disclose your information including your personal identity if we believe such action is necessary to comply with law and regulation for investigation, for protecting intellectual properties, user rights, respond to queries and for the safety of Sweet Sharing , users and others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## What About Other Websites Linked to This Site?

There are many websites that are linked to our website. We can’t take responsibility for those websites. Usually we refer to other websites for additional information which we think valuable to our users. Once you navigate to other website our Privacy Policy will no longer be in effect, your browsing and interaction with that website is subject to their privacy policy. Please read their rules and policies before proceeding.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

In case there is any change in the privacy policy in the future, we will notify the users through emails & publish the same on our website.

## Your Consent

By using this site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, the same will be intimated to you through the website. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy please feel free to submit your queries via email to **[nag.garima@gmail.com](mailto:nag.garima@gmail.com "mailto:nag.garima@gmail.com")**  We will undertake reasonable efforts to resolve or address your concern.
